{
    "title": "What Colour is That?",
	"questions":
		{
			"Question 1":
				[
					{ "question": "What colour is the ocean?"},
					{ "correct answer": "Blue" },
					{ "potential answer": [
                        "Red", "Orange", "Yellow", "Green", "Indigo", "Violet"
                        ]
                    }
				],
			"Question 2":
				[
					{ "question": "What colour is a lemon?"},
					{ "correct answer": "Yellow" },
					{ "potential answer": [
                        "Red", "Orange", "Blue", "Green", "Indigo", "Violet"
                        ]
                    }
				],
			"Question 3":
				[
					{ "question": "What colour is a firetruck?"},
					{ "correct answer": "Red" },
					{ "potential answer": [
                        "Yellow", "Orange", "Blue", "Green", "Indigo", "Violet"
                        ]
                    }
				],
			"Question 4":
				[
					{ "question": "What colour is grass?"},
					{ "correct answer": "Green" },
					{ "potential answer": [
                        "Red", "Orange", "Blue", "Yellow", "Indigo", "Violet"
                        ]
                    }
				],
			"Question 5":
				[
					{ "question": "What colour is a pumpkin?"},
					{ "correct answer": "Orange" },
					{ "potential answer": [
                        "Red", "Yellow", "Blue", "Green", "Indigo", "Violet"
                        ]
                    }
				],
			"Question 6":
				[
					{ "question": "What colour is an eggplant?"},
					{ "correct answer": "Violet" },
					{ "potential answer": [
                        "Red", "Orange", "Blue", "Green", "Indigo", "Yellow"
                        ]
                    }
				],
			"Question 7":
				[
					{ "question": "What colour are indigos??"},
					{ "correct answer": "Indigo" },
					{ "potential answer": [
                        "Red", "Orange", "Blue", "Green", "Yellow", "Violet"
                        ]
                    }
				],
			"Question 8":
				[
					{ "question": "What colour is a lemon??"},
					{ "correct answer": "Yellow" },
					{ "potential answer": [
                        "Red", "Orange", "Blue", "Green", "Indigo", "Violet"
                        ]
                    }
				],
			"Question 9":
				[
					{ "question": "What colour is a lemon??"},
					{ "correct answer": "Yellow" },
					{ "potential answer": [
                        "Red", "Orange", "Blue", "Green", "Indigo", "Violet"
                        ]
                    }
				],
			"Question 10":
				[
					{ "question": "What colour is a lemon??"},
					{ "correct answer": "Yellow" },
					{ "potential answer": [
                        "Red", "Orange", "Blue", "Green", "Indigo", "Violet"
                        ]
                    }
				]
		}
        

}